Hello friends, in this video we will talk about
friends, this is a bear price of 1660,
what happened after that, it
started to decline friends and here this low was placed
at this price, this low of 2014 was placed,
what has happened since then, there has been a breakout in big volume,
with the gossip happening, it is
currently moving on the weekly chart, friends, it is moving at
this price of 1370 and is
forming a range here, friends, okay, whenever a
bear price breaks out in big volume with a big downfall,
after that
whenever a range is formed to go up, friends, if a
range is formed in this way, then the G
side of the range will break out or if it breaks out
or breaks down, then it shows a big mouth,
if this price comes, it broke out at 1332, it can reach
this level again,
but if it breaks the level of 142 or 49, in
this way the
discussion will become a direct target, friends,
which is of 167, the biggest thing in this type of discussion is that the
volume is very
aggressive, buyers dominant.  They are doing this
to Sir and they want this Sir to
go till here friends,
so if it gets stopped then
its stop loss is 1332 which is this price
and our Ben level will start from
1400, as soon as it crosses, we will bike
in this candle and will keep the target
of 1600 friends because buying
dominance is visible here friends, so
this target will be achieved easily friends, so
friends, for such videos you should
subscribe to this channel friends, thank
you.